I hate California want to go East Coast I want
to go where culture it like me Morgan I recently
Connecticut or New me Morgan I recently Connecticut or New Hampshire
and writers live in the Hampshire and writers live in the women's
of those schools anyway mom women's of those schools anyway mom should
just go to City College you know with your work
ethic just go to City College and then to jail
back and then to City College and then maybe you'd
to City College and then maybe you'd learn to pull
yourself up and not expect everybody to do everything Lady
Bird is that your given name yeah why is it
in quotes I gave it to myself it's given me
by Lady Bird always says that she lives in the
wrong side of tracks but I always thought that the tracks but I always thought that
was like a metaphor but there are actual train tracks
what she did was actual train tracks what she did was very
baller introduced
she has a very baller introduced she has a big
heart ear mom she's warm but also kind of scary
you can't be and warm I think you can your
mom is so you're not interested in any Catholic you're not interested in any Catholic colleges
no way high schools like Yale colleges no way high schools like Yale but
not because I probably couldn't but not Yale because I probably couldn't get
in you definitely couldn't get in you definitely couldn't get in does
mom hate me you're tired we can sit up I'm
not tying or dragging your feet you are so infuriating
stop yo I'm not yelling Oh perfect love it you
both have such strong
when is a normal time do you have sex you're
having
just wanted it to be special why you're gonna have
so much done why you're gonna have so much done special
sex in your life we're afraid special sex in your life we're afraid that
we will never escape our past that we will never escape our past whatever
we give you it's never enough whatever we give you it's never enough
we're afraid of what it's never enough we're afraid of what the
future will bring we're afraid we the future will bring we're afraid we won't
be loved
like yeah well you know your mom totally
and we won't succeed I want you to be the
very best version of yourself that you could
what if this is the best version
what I'd really like us to be on math Olympiad
but isn't something you're Olympiad but math isn't something you're very
strong in that we know of yet